What's with the gun?
We need to bring him back.
Can't let 'em take his powers away.
If we can't stop them…
then we'll have to bring 'em down.
I caught him, Dad. Piece of cake.
Caught?
Yeah, I've got this.
I'm gonna take care of it myself.
I shouldn't have come here.
Shit, really?
-Ugh, this thing.
-Can I ask you a question?
I was wondering…
Why would you walk in here?
'Cause it'd be so easy to kill you.
You're completely helpless.
Not that I'd actually do it.
I'm just saying I could do it.
-Get started.
-Yes, ma'am.
Finish the extraction,
then kill him when you're done.
The reason why I'm here?
Because I wanted to be normal.
And to do that,
I had to join the Society of Superhumans
in order to take you on
so we could guarantee our safety
and protect our interests.
What?
My power's my inheritance.
It's not for sale.
Understand?
Let 'em have it, Bun-mi.
-Get down!
-The money.
Shoot him already!
Hey, what the fuck is going on?
I'm guessing you wanna know what happened.
The truth,
I had to rely on my raw instincts.
After proposing the truce,
the Mundane Vanguard began surveilling us.
MUNDANE
Given the circumstances,
it seemed impossible
to sneak our way into the lab
without them knowing.
We had one option.
Hey, Bun-mi.
We had to fool ourselves
into believing our own lie.
Do with this information what you will.
Wait for my signal at the final moment.
I trust you.
Hey, I almost died!
Why did you plan something
so ridiculous and elaborate?
Wow. 'Cause I wasn't able to trust you.
I'm sorry, didn't you write "I trust you"?
That message was for Bun-mi.
Over there.
There's the safe.
You've gotten good at breaking into safes.
It was hard at first,
but now I got the hang of it.
This is…
BEOMHA RANCH
Take the files.
-Whoa!
-Go, go, go! Hurry, this way!
-These guys are…
-Oh my God!
MY MIN-SUK
Are you okay?
-Two days away.
-Mm?
Our dinner. Our families united.
Two days?
Why are you just telling me this now?
Oh, this nice restaurant
had a special offer so…
50% off. A last-minute online sale.
Oh! Hey! Wait! No, wait, wait!
Hey! My money!
Oh no.
Ah! No way!
What? What's wrong?
This is a really expensive restaurant.
We need the coupon.
Sounds good.
It's a nonrefundable discount voucher.
Call your parents now and let them know.
This Friday, dinner at 7:00.
Okay.
We gotta go, Sang-ung.
Right.
-You still got booze, right?
-You still got cash, right?
If a superhuman
doesn't have their superpower,
that just makes them human.
Now, I finally get what
my dad was talking about.
Superpowers, it's not like
they're that big a deal.
Hmm.
-Whoa!
BEOMHA RANCH
I'm ready for whatever
I am ready to roll
You good?
Every move I make, I'm breaking free
To live this moment
Never looking back…
She's certifiably crazy.
My yesterday
We're turning the page…
Hurry. Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Feeling the rush, new day begins
Making the most of every day
Every scar and every tear
They made me who I am
For in this brand-new day
There's just nothing left to hide
Forget about yesterday
Forget it
I had four billion.
It slipped away just like that.
I would think
you're used to being strapped for cash.
With four billion, I could…
Are you crying?
Oh, I'm okay.
All good.
Another day for the Cashero.
You've gone off the deep end.
Evil bastards.
They're experimenting on people illegally.
I'm not sure what their plan is,
but whatever it is,
they need our powers to make it work.
A NEW BUSINESS MODEL
UTILIZING DEPENDENCY AND HALLUCINATION
What is it? What's it say they're doing?
Well, it looks like their plan is, uh,
to make something.
During the process
of restoring superpower proteins.
This is for you.
TO SANG-UNG
"I really admire you."
"Helping all those people
and never taking the credit."
"That's the kind of hero the world needs."
Jo Nathan.
Jo Nathan?
I've never seen
that name before. It's cool.
NAME: JO NATHAN
Jo Nathan the name.
You know, I see all that you do.
Helping all those people.
Always in secret.
The thing is,
I'm also working on a secret plan
that will change the world.
JO NATHAN
Wow.
What a shame, Jo Anna.
Dad is gonna hate this.
How's it feel to be back in Korea?
Not bad at all.
The chairman moved them all
to Gimhae Bank.
They're already there.
It doesn't matter.
The thing I really want
isn't there anyway.
Are we ready?
Yes, it's all done.
Let's start then.
RESTRICTED AREA
RESIDENCY FORM
APRIL 2025
JO NATHAN
UNIT 2302, CHANGIL PARKTRIUM
This is Jo Nathan's place?
A civil servant looking up
someone's address is illegal, old man.
Couldn't you get in trouble for that?
It is. You're right.
Report me if you want.
Get ready.
The place is empty.
Huh.
It seems like he hasn't moved in yet.
Oh, he has.
Huh.
What's wrong? What is it?
Hold on a minute.
He's down there.
Just like a three-headed dragon,
when you chop off one head,
an uglier, more evil one takes its place.
STATEMENT OF HOUSING ACQUISITION FINANCING
AND OCCUPANCY PLAN
REQUIRED DOCUMENT
FOR REAL ESTATE TRANSACTION
REAL ESTATE TRANSACTION
CORPORATE DECLARATION
Don't push yourself too hard.
Heat up the rice and soup,
and eat it before you go to bed.
It was your turn to cook tonight,
you know.
Come home early tomorrow.
I wonder how those superheroes
in the movies manage to fight
all the evil villains
while also maintaining a family
and holding down a day job.
I admire them.
Looks delicious.
Mr. Kang.
What in the world have you been up to
that would make the police department
come looking for you?
It's a misunderstanding, sir. Very minor.
Hmm.
Write a discipline report
about your taking a work vehicle
and for leaving early
without authorization.
Get ready for a pay cut.
Uh, uh, a pay cut?
Oh, but why though?
Why do you think?
'Cause those are the rules here.
-It'll be for three months.
-Oh my…
Three months? Are you serious?
Cutting one-third of my current salary
makes my wage just above the poverty line.
To make it even worse,
if Min-suk finds out about this,
being kicked out of the middle class
will be the least of my worries.
What? We're done.
Was there something else?
I'm sorry.
Would it be all right if I left early?
If I took a half day today?
NOTICE TO APPEAR
SUSPECT INTERROGATION REPORT
Your name is, uh, Kang Sang-ung.
Am I correct?
Yeah.
NAME: KANG SANG-UNG
Don't feel pressured to respond.
It was just my name.
They could use it against you.
Saying my name?
We both saw each other that time
at the community center, right?
My client says
he does not recall any meeting.
This is what a CEO
must feel like giving a deposition.
-You're here.
-Yeah.
Just wait outside.
Long time, no see.
I knew you were involved.
You still carrying on with this nonsense?
Of course.
Who else will?
Is this your new lackey?
-Hey!
-Yeah?
The hell were you thinking,
risking your life? You're married too.
What are you, a police officer?
A firefighter?
No. No, sir. I… I'm nothing at all.
I have some advice.
Stop while you're ahead.
If you cause any more trouble,
I'll make sure you get locked up for it.
Is that clear?
Hey. Do you know who that detective is?
-He was one of us.
-A superhuman?
Are you serious?
So what's his power?
He's good at picking fights.
Wait a second.
Why's he bringing me in
in the first place?
Is he Mundane Vanguard?
We just don't have the same point of view.
Everything's okay. Don't worry.
I don't know how not to worry.
-He… he said he'd send me to prison--
-I've got it under control.
No, it's all right.
I've been cutting carbs recently.
God, that's such horseshit.
You should keep an eye on your health now
if you wanna live long.
You haven't changed at all
since you were little.
Always running your mouth
and saying nothing.
Gee. I should've just killed you
when I had the chance.
What happened?
I had 'em all drugged.
The replication of powers
is what we're after.
How do you know that?
I'm part of this family. Of course I know.
It was pretty much
just one big clinical trial.
They're covering it on the news
all day, every day right now.
What's the point of us
drawing unwanted attention?
I mean, Dad.
This idiot's purposely trying
to bring everything down.
You're right about one thing.
It was on purpose.
So Kang Sang-ung would see.
You're so full of shit.
Father. Do you know
what's in every hero's nature?
How they love meddling.
Sticking their noses
where they don't belong.
They can't ignore things.
They've gotta do something.
He's gonna look for me soon. I know it.
I will lure this "hero" to a location
where I have the advantage.
From now on,
I want you to take control
of the lab work.
Dad, please.
It's the bleeding of the masses
that allows our coffers to fill up.
Let's eat.
You were questioned by the police?
When you go to prison,
don't mention any of our names, please.
I told you not to joke around.
This is serious. I'm freaking out here.
Now that you're done reading all of that,
the names for their clinical trial.
Apparently, six people on that list
were among the ones we saw jump yesterday.
The Mundane Vanguard
is conducting experiments
on ordinary citizens.
MUNDANE
Experiments are being conducted
around the clubbing scene in Gangnam.
It's popular 'cause it causes
intense hallucinations.
The supplier is
a merchandise distributor called Hermes.
Their name is Hermes?
They carry
a different colored designer bag each day.
I've received intel that Hermes
will be at a club called Mecenat
tomorrow afternoon.
Let's catch Hermes as quickly as possible
and get the drugs.
After their clinical trials, they'll start
replicating powers so they can sell them.
Before there are more casualties,
we gotta stop these guys…
at all costs.
HOTTEST AFFORDABLE SPEC-UP IN BULK
DEALER: HERMES
Hey, I'm home.
Oh, you're back.
What's all this?
Are we moving?
Take your clothes off.
-Huh? Right now?
-Mm-hmm.
I don't have any cash.
-Give me a minute.
-We're not doing that.
You need something to wear
for our parents.
Oh, that's right. Our official dinner.
Why didn't you answer your phone all day?
Did something happen?
I left my phone in my bag.
I didn't see your calls. Forgive me.
-Oh.
-It needs to be okay.
This isn't how a marriage usually unfolds.
Marriage registration,
subscription savings account,
proposal, then our official dinner?
If the official first dinner
with our parents goes wrong,
then everything that Min-suk and I
have been working towards
will go right down the drain.
Uh-huh. This one's great.
-Try it on for me.
-Okay.
This is really nice.
Hey. What'd you spend
so much money on this suit for?
It's our official dinner.
Keep it spotless.
It was over a million won?
You don't even buy clothes
this expensive for yourself.
You're schedule's open, right?
Of course it is. Yep. Uh-huh.
You look great. 7:00 sharp at Jongno.
It's important.
I know, honey.
Mm.
-If I'm late. I'll fly there.
-Oh my God.
It's in case of emergency only.
Don't be stupid.
Yeah, don't worry.
Wait. Could I borrow another 50?
-Not today.
-That's okay.
-See you in a bit.
-Mm-hmm.
Later.
See ya!
It takes an hour
to get from Gangnam to Jongno.
I'll catch Hermes by six o'clock,
then make it
for our official parents' dinner at 7:00.
I can do this.
Where are you?
We're in.
Can't believe I'm in a club
on the day of our sacred official dinner.
What the hell has my life become?
So what's with this outfit you got on?
This, coming from a guy who looks dressed
for a Gukbingwan crowd.
Gukbingwan? Hey, you know,
this suit is designer.
The people in here sure know how to party.
Hey, where'd you get that?
Show your bracelet at the bar.
Everything's free under 5,000 won.
The drinks at these things
are all covered by company funds. Right?
Hey, spread your wings a little.
Don't drink bottom shelf.
Order the most expensive one. Go on.
There's one that's a hundred million won.
I think you made a good choice.
Any idea how to find Hermes
in this craziness?
ATTORNEY BYEON
IMAGE SENT
FIND A RED BAG
Byeon sent us a pic of the handbag.
It's red.
Oh, come on.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry, guys.
Too chunky.
Sorry about that. Sorry.
This sucks. So many red ones.
They all look so similar.
It's confusing.
It's red.
-That purse is yours?
-Yeah, that's right.
Hey, motherfucker.
Are you insane? Watch it, man.
You boys should get going.
Your next order will be free.
Let's get out of here.
Perfect. I can make it
to our official dinner in time.
We haven't met.
You're Hermes.
Mr. Kang Sang-ung?
You and I have some business.
We need to sort it out.
You did a good job finding your way here.
To be honest,
I didn't think you'd make it.
What business? Tell me.
Well, she doesn't sound menacing at all.
If things go sideways,
I might be a little late.
Oh, I didn't know you were one of us.
Do you wanna join the society?
We get together and drink tea. It's fun.
I'll give you an application.
You walk around with this little?
Well, I had a pay cut
on top of everything else.
It's been really hard.
Well, after that,
you'll never be able to join us.
Jo Nathan, the managing director,
he wants me to bring you in.
Yeah, that might be difficult
'cause I already have other plans tonight.
Hey.
Take your shot. Go on!
It's not like I can see her.
Oh. Sang Ung.
Unbelievable. Brand-new.
What on earth? Huh?
-Whoa! Your suit.
-Attorney Byeon.
Go.
Hermes is a superhuman.
-I have the drugs. We're on our way out.
-She's a superhuman? Really?
That's right. Stay alert.
Let's get outta here.
You're angry.
'Cause I told you to let him hit you?
With his powers, I feel like
I could just bring him in myself.
That wouldn't be fun.
Oh, uh, sorry. Excuse me.
Ah, just trying to get through. Excuse us.
Ah, what? What the hell?
What are they doing?
Whoa!
FOR YOU, WHO WORKS FOR OTHERS
EVEN WITHOUT RECOGNITION
Jo Nathan's here.
Clubs aren't usually like this, are they?
Everyone wants to become someone special.
What?
YOU CAN BE SPECIAL TOO
Let's go.
But speaking as someone
who has experienced it,
I swear to you, and take my word for it,
it's much better to be normal.
-Bun-mi!
-Sang-ung!
What's happening?
If the drugs get taken away,
everyone
will die.
What a crime to be broke. That poor guy.
He can't do anything without money?
Can he?
Sang-ung, are you there?
Bun-mi, answer.
MY MIN-SUK
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable. Please leave a…
I get the feeling that
the date we set for our official dinner
wasn't the most ideal.